[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Let's say Mikoy's intel is valid.
The next question is, is it actionable?
If we don't act now and go to Italy right away,
we'll end up wasting the intel we have.
What guarantee do we have that this mission will be successful?
What guarantee do we have that we'll all make it back alive?
I failed Mikoy,
but definitely,
I cannot let my mission fail.
I hope this mission can change you back.
As much as my brain can't imagine
you and Chiara getting back together, but you know,
I'm genuinely rooting for the two of you.
Because I know you're just caught in a situation.
After all is said and done,
let's just wait and see how this ends.
Son, why did you have to go back to that agency?
Mom, I'm really sorry.
Mom, I have to do this for Dad.
For Mario?
I've already made my decision.
And I'm fully committed to this mission.
But revenge isn't the answer, son.
I know you have good intentions.
You have a good heart.
Mikoy.
You know, I know how heavy the burden you're carrying is.
But revenge isn't the answer, son.
It's still wrong.
Because Mikoy, this isn't you.
You're not the kind of person who seeks revenge.
And you're not someone who can kill.
Especially not the person you love most.
Lord, please forgive me.
I know what I'm about to do is a sin.
Are you Mikoy Pinagpala?
Yes.
That's me.
I have some important information for you.
Chiara and her group will be traveling from Prague
to meet with the Castellanis.
Is that new intel from your source?
Chiara's meeting is definitely scheduled with the Castellanis.
This is valuable intel.
So, sir, you're approving this mission?
I called Malacañang last night,
and believe it or not,
the Office of the President had already given its approval.
Operation Italiani commences.
-Thank you. -Thank you.
Oh, you still found time to eat, huh?
Are you sure about your lead?
Of course, I'm absolutely sure.
You know, I really like the sandwich you're eating.
Is it good?
It's okay.
I just saw people lining up for it.
So I figured I'd line up too.
You're such a bandwagoner.
You know, people really love putting labels on others, don't they?
It makes it easier to avoid the people you don't like.
So, now that I'm a bandwagoner,
does that mean
you don't like me anymore?
You're the longest-serving police asset I've ever had.
So at this point,
after all these years we've been together,
it'd be impossible for me not to like you.
How can I help you?
I'm just looking for directions.
Okay, where do you want to go?
Do you want to go to my heart?
-Maybe. -Really?
But first, I need to go here.
This. You know this place?
That's why I want to go
-because I want to complain to the Pope! -Yes?
-Excuse me. -Hey!
Where are you? He's heading your way.
Already moving?
Yes, and hurry.
I can't follow him because he might get suspicious of me,
and he can't realize that his phone is missing.
So you better be on your way,
or we'll lose our chance to get La Fornarina.
Just tell me which direction he's going.
I will distract him.
Are you sure?
What?
That's the direction he went.
Thank you.
My informant says that's their meeting place.
Let's just follow this guy.
Why?
You think I still have feelings for her?
That could compromise the mission.
Because if you did,
after what she did to you and your family,
I'd be the one to smash a rock over your head myself.
I'm just making sure you can do what we need to do.
Just like you said, right?
I'm not the same Mikoy you knew.
At least this way, my father's death will get justice.
What are we waiting for?
Wow, the view is beautiful!
Look how beautiful it is!
Of course!
And did you know?
They say,
and this is just gossip,
but apparently,
this is where Napoleon Bonaparte stayed.
If I had been alive back then,
I would've told him not to go to Waterloo.
If he hadn't gone to Waterloo,
then that ABBA song would not exist.
Right?
But over there,
that's where they're supposed to meet.
Inside the restaurant.
Maybe you can park the car over here.
Do you remember the first time we sent you out
to plant a surveillance and listening device?
But now you have everything under control.
You're so different from the Mikoy I knew.
You know,
I would give everything
to go back to the life I had before.
The Mikoy who used to mess everything up.
Like you said, someone who always panics.
Always nervous.
The one who knew nothing about these things.
You know?
Why are you sorry?
Because if it weren't for me,
your life probably wouldn't have become this messy and complicated.
So you believe that because of you,
my life stopped being happy and fell apart?
You know, Alex,
I can always look back at my life
and wonder what if I had done this,
or what if I had done that instead.
One big decision.
One mistake I'll have to pay for.
I gave my heart to the wrong person.
That's all it is.
Because you know, honestly,
you're not really a coward or a nervous person.
As a matter of fact,
you're the bravest person I've ever met.
I also know that…
the world has been cruel to you lately.
Continue believing in love.
Despite the world not believing on it.
Our subject is moving.
Let's go.
What's your wish?
An average of 1.6 million euros
worth of coins are tossed
into fountains like these.
Imagine,
1.6 million euros, approximately 180 million pesos,
just to make a wish we all know won't come true.
They call us criminals, a syndicate,
but aren't they the ones
who are actually the syndicate and criminals?
I hope your wish is that everything goes smoothly tomorrow.
What? Ready?
Alex and I will pretend to be a couple on their honeymoon.
The background you're seeing behind me is called Piazza del Popolo.
This will also be Chiara's meeting place
with the leader of the Castellani family.
The godfather and patriarch of the Castellani family.
Nancy Castiglione?
None of you know Nancy Castiglione?
The Nancy Castiglione?
She's one of the stars
of my all-time favorite movie.
AsBoobs.
Or Asal Bobo the Movie.
She later reinvented herself
as a musical artist,
as Nancy Jane.
Cocoy.
Castellani family.
Not Castiglione.
Can we go back to Mikoy's briefing?
Yes, sir.
Francesco Castellani.
Why does La Fornarina need
to meet with the Castellani family?
My informant told me that the Castellani family
is the last holdout and the last true threat
to Chiara's power as principale.
Or leader of the Concordat.
If she gets their support,
then Chiara's hold on power over all the mafias in Europe will strengthen.
No one will dare challenge her anymore.
And from this position,
I will have the perfect line of sight
to everyone entering and leaving the restaurant,
and all I need is one shot to take her out.
And what will Mikoy do?
I'm just giving them a chance because of you.
I told you,
it's better to talk things out than to try killing each other.
That's also my struggle, Agent Dara.
But as far as Chiara is alive,
we will not be safe.
I know he won't stop
until he gets justice for his father's death.
Of all people,
you're the one who knows Agent Sianong more.
But I understand him more.
Because in other areas of life,
we are the same.
We both love someone who is in love with someone else.